https://jhberge.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Privacy Statement
This statement discloses the Privacy Policy for J & H Berge® website (jhberge.com).
This site has been designed so that no personal identifying information is accessible to the general public.
You may browse J & H Berg® online catalog without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.
To obtain access to special features and for ordering we ask that you register.
Use of Data
For ordering and operations purposes, we will collect the necessary data to process your request. We do not sell or distribute that personal information to any third party except to complete transactions with our freight companies and our suppliers that are authorized to ship orders on our behalf.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use SSL security, a highly effective and recognized software that encrypts transactions as they are in transit to and from our servers. Additionally, we have purchased an independent third party licensing service license to ensure the security of our site
Registration
When you register as a customer, you will provide us with your basic contact information and address information. This information will allow you the user, to access to certain parts of the site and helps us process your transactions. The user may change or omit information in their account, but this will delay the processing of your transactions. We do not store any credit/debit card information on the JHBerge.com website.
Links
JHBerge.com may contain links to other Websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another Web site. The new site may have a different privacy policy than TheJHBerge.com and the content found on that site is not the responsibility of J & H Berge, Inc. / The LabMart. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites for these purposes.
We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.
Cookies
JHBerge.com uses software tags called "cookies" to identify customers and track shopping baskets when they visit the site. These "cookies" benefit the customer by allowing them to stay logged in during their visit. It also allows selected products within a shopping basket to remain as a customer goes to other areas to browse. We cannot provide a totally secured shopping experience to users whose browsers are set to reject cookies.
J & H Berge® / The LabMart® reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted on our website for review and will be effective immediately.
Last update 10/19/2017
Back
Information
About J&H Berge
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
